Finding Aid for the SOUL Publications, Inc. records PASC-M.0342
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 3. Audio Cassettes, 1969-1980
  - Diane Steinberg (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Diane Steinberg by Judy Spiegelman, 1978 February 24 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - John Amos interview at SOUL, 1977 January 6 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Theodore Pendergrass by Tsuyoko Sako (Box 61, Folder 10)
    Also commonly known as Teddy Pendergrass
  - Andrew Young, Brotherhood Crusade, 1978 May 6 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Philippe Wynne, 1977 January 15 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Labelle (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - White Shadow by Mike Terry and Leonard Pitts, 1979 January 11 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Stevie Wonder press conference, 1976 April 13 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Stevie Wonder by Lee Underwood (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Stevie's mother's birthday party and Stevie and Minnie gold record, 1976 January 15 and 1975 November 10 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    Refers to Stevie Wonder and Minnie Riperton
  - Philip Thomas by Connie Johnson, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Also known as Philip Michael Thomas
  - Mary Wilson, 1976 July 21 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Paul Winfield (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Bill Withers part I, 1975 October 16 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Bill Withers parts II and III, 1975 October 16 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Bill Withers by Tsuyoko Sako and Albert Popwell (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Bill Withers is on side 1; Albert Popwell is on side 2
  - Buster Jones, 1973 April 3 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Mick Jagger by Regina Jones, 1978 August 16 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Jesse Jackson (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Emotions, 1977 January 8 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Brothers Johnson, 1976 February 23 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Rick James by Leonard Pitts (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Muhammad Ali (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Dogs O War, 1977 March (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Randy Crawford by Janet Robinson, 1976 December 22 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Stymie (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Natalie Cole (Box 62, Folder 17)
- 4. Photographs, 1962-1996
  Photographs, proof sheets, photomechanical prints, slides, and negatives, with some press releases and biographies attached to photographs.
  - Barbara Acklin (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Little Anthony and the Imperials, ca. 1966-1976 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Includes some photographs of Little Anthony's solo career; see also the Imperials, box 67, folder 11
  - Debbie Allen (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Cholly Atkins, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Ashford & Simpson, ca. 1972-1980 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - First Choice (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Yvonne Fair, ca. 1975 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Mike Evans, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Elgins (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Brenda Lee Eager (Box 63, Folder 10)
    See also Jerry Butler, box 63, folder 18
  - Miscellaneous E, ca. 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Archie Bell and the Drells, ca. 1975-1977 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Blue Magic (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes, ca. 1973-1978 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Includes photographs of Teddy Pendergrass
  - Johnny Bristol, ca. 1974-1976 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Jim Brown (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Peabo Bryson, ca. 1978 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Jerry Butler, ca. 1970-1978 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous A and B (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - G.C. Cameron (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Clarence Carter, undated (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Mel Carter, ca. 1973-1974 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Chairmen of the Board (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Chic (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Gene Chandler, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Chi-Lites, ca. 1973-1976 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Contours (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Marc Copage (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Randy Crawford, ca. 1975-1983 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Merry Clayton, ca. 1968 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Norman Connors (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Linda Clifford (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous C, ca. 1975-1995 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous J, ca. 1980-1995 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Jose Feliciano (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Friends of Distinction (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Betty Everett, undated (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Damon Evans, ca. 1975 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous D (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Dramatics (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Bill Withers, ca. 1976-1979 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Nat and Maria Cole, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    Includes images of Nat "King" Cole and his wife Maria
  - Miscellaneous F (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Diahann Carroll, ca. 1974-1976 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Blossoms, ca. 1968-1971 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Nancy Wilson (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Natalie Cole (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - James Brown -- miscellaneous prints, ca. 1966-1980 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - James Brown -- proof sheets and negatives, ca. 1969-1977 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Emotions (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Lola Falana (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Clifton Davis, ca. 1974-1979 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Hal Davis, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Sarah Dash (Box 64, Folder 16)
    See also Labelle, box 69, folder 1
  - Darcus, ca. 1978 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Damion & Denita, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Commodores -- miscellaneous prints (Box 65, Folder 1)
    See also Lionel Ritchie, box 76, folder 3
  - Commodores -- proof sheets, ca. 1977-1979 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Tony Orlando and Dawn (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Dells (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Carol Douglas, ca. 1974-1977 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Delfonics, ca. 1970-1975 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Fifth Dimension -- miscellaneous prints (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Fifth Dimension -- performance-related (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Fifth Dimension -- Marilyn McCoo, ca. 1972-1982 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    Includes photographs from her career after departing the Fifth Dimension; see also Fifth Dimension -- miscellaneous prints, box 65, folder 7; Fifth Dimension -- performance- related, box 65, folder 8
  - Five Stairsteps, ca. 1968-1976 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    Also known as the Stairsteps
  - Roberta Flack (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Aretha Franklin -- miscellaneous prints, ca. 1970-1980 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Aretha Franklin -- proof sheets and negatives, ca. 1968-1978 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Earth, Wind & Fire (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Four Tops (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Junius Griffin, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Marc Gordon, undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Marla Gibbs (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Cuba Gooding (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Fame, ca. 1980 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Gloria Gaynor, ca. 1975-1979 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Al Green (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Honeycone (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Lena Horne, ca. 1974-1983 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - HOT, ca. 1977-1979 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Hodges, James & Smith (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous G (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Patrice Holloway, ca. 1970-1980 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Brenda Holloway, ca. 1966-1970 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Lamont Dozier (Box 66, Folder 18)
    Refers to the former member of Holland-Dozier-Holland
  - Thelma Houston, ca. 1970-1980 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Donny Hathaway, undated (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Harlettes (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Whitney Houston, ca. 1986-1996 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - High Inergy, ca. 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Nona Hendryx (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Isaac Hayes, ca. 1973-1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Bertha Gordy, 1975 February 2 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Refers to the mother of Motown founder Berry Gordy, Jr.; includes photographs and proof sheets from her funeral
  - Berry Gordy IV (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Refers to the son of Motown founder Berry Gordy, Jr.
  - Berry Gordy, Jr., ca. 1969-1977 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Refers to founder of Motown
  - Berry Gordy, Jr. and Motown, ca. 1969-1976 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Hues Corporation (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Willie Hutch, ca. 1974-1979 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Phyllis Hyman, ca. 1976-1979 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous H (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Impact (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Imperials, ca. 1976-1979 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    See also Little Anthony and the Imperials, box 63, folder 2
  - Leon Isaac Kennedy, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Impressions (Box 67, Folder 13)
    See also Curtis Mayfield, box 69, folder 11
  - Miscellaneous I, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Isley Brothers, ca. 1969-1978 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Jesse Jackson (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Jay and the Techniques, undated (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Mable John, ca. 1973-1976 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Al Jarreau (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Etta James (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Rick James, ca. 1978-1980 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - B.B. King, ca. 1973-1979 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Grace Jones (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Evelyn "Champagne" King (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Eartha Kitt, ca. 1974-1979 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Kool and the Gang, ca. 1974-1980 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. and family (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Rufus (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Includes photographs of Chaka Khan as lead singer and of Chaka Khan's solo career
  - Quincy Jones, ca. 1973-1981 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Margie Joseph, ca. 1974-1978 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Eloise Laws (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Lara Lee, undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Love Unlimited, ca. 1974-1980 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Love Lites (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous K (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Stacey Lattisaw, undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1973-1992 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Gladys Knight & the Pips (folder 2 of 2) (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Labelle (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Includes a few photographs relating to the solo careers of group members; also see Sarah Dash, box 64, folder 16; Nona Hendryx, box 66, folder 24; Patti LaBelle, box 76, folder 13
  - Cheryl Lynn, ca. 1978-1980 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous L, ca. 1981-1992 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Marvelettes (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Manhattans, ca. 1976-1980 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Miriam Makeba, ca. 1975 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Main Ingredient (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Moms Mabley (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Barbara Mason, ca. 1977-1980 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Miracles, ca. 1973-1976 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    Includes photographs of the group with Bill Griffin as front man, after Smokey Robinson's departure; see also Smokey Robinson, box 71, folder 8
  - Curtis Mayfield (Box 69, Folder 11)
    See also the Impressions, box 67, folder 13
  - Ray, Goodman & Brown, ca. 1970-1980 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    Also includes photographs under the group's previous name, the Moments
  - Melba Moore, ca. 1976-1979 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Teena Marie (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Alton McClain & Destiny, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Mirettes, ca. 1966-1970 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    The group was formerly known as the Ikettes
  - Carmen McRae (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Stephanie Mills, ca. 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Barbara McNair, ca. 1968-1970 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Van McCoy (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Johnny Nash (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Bryan O'Dell, ca. 1978 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Lonette McKee, ca. 1975 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    See also Sparkle, box 72, folder 2
  - Miscellaneous O (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous N, ca. 1973-1996 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Denise Nicholas, ca. 1975-1980 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Ron O' Neal (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous M (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Lou Rawls, ca. 1968-1980 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous P, ca. 1978-1996 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Rare Earth (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Includes photographs of the band Rare Earth, which was affiliated with Motown's Rare Earth label
  - Quindon, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Quiet Elegance, ca. 1973 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Platters (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Billy Preston, ca. 1970-1977 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Sidney Poitier, ca. 1968-1976 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Ray Parker (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Freda Payne (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Peaches & Herb, ca. 1968-1981 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Billy Paul, ca. 1971-1978 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Wilson Pickett (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - LaWanda Page (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Bonnie Pointer, ca. 1979 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    See also Pointer Sisters, box 71, folder 1
  - Righteous Brothers, ca. 1968-1975 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Della Reese (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Time, ca. 1981 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    See also Prince, box 70, folder 25
  - Prince, ca. 1978-1982 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    Scope and Content
    Eight 8x10 black and white glossies of Prince. 1 duplicate.
    Warner Brothers Records Media Information re Controversy, and a Prince Bio.
    See also the Time, box 70, folder 24; Vanity, box 73, folder 2.
  - Pointer Sisters (Box 71, Folder 1)
    See also Bonnie Pointer, box 70, folder 21
  - Minnie Riperton, ca. 1974-1979 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Martha Reeves, ca. 1966-1979 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Includes some photographs with the Vandellas
  - T-Boy Ross (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous R, ca. 1981-1996 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Otis Redding, ca. 1966-1975 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Ritchie Family (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Smokey Robinson (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Includes some photographs with the Miracles; see also Miracles, box 69, folder 10; Smokey Robinson -- proof sheets and negatives, box 76, folder 10
  - Sly and the Family Stone, ca. 1973-1975 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Danielle Spencer, ca. 1977-1979 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Dwan Smith (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Sister Sledge, ca. 1973-1980 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Side Effect, ca. 1978-1980 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    Includes photographs of Sylvia St. James
  - Shalamar (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Sam & Dave, ca. 1966-1972 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Dee Dee Sharp, ca. 1977 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    She is also known as Dee Dee Sharp Gamble
  - Edwin Starr (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Sylvester, ca. 1978-1980 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    Includes photographs with the Two Tons O' Fun (Izora Rhodes and Martha Wash); see also Two Tons O' Fun, box 72, folder 18
  - Miscellaneous S, ca. 1974-1996 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Syreeta (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Switch, ca. 1978 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Candi Staton, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Barrett Strong (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Sparkle (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Refers to the 1976 film; see also Lonette McKee, box 70, folder 1; Dwan Smith, box 71, folder 11; Philip Michael Thomas, box 72, folder 13
  - Nina Simone, ca. 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Sisters Love, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - O'Jays -- miscellaneous prints (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - O'Jays -- proof sheets, ca. 1973-1977 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Cicely Tyson, ca. 1978 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Three Degrees (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Three Ounces of Love (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Peter Tosh, ca. 1976-1979 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Third World, ca. 1976-1979 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Joe Tex (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Philip Michael Thomas (Box 72, Folder 13)
    He was also known simply as Philip Thomas in the early stages of his career; see also Sparkle, box 72, folder 2
  - Johnnie Taylor, ca. 1975 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Staple Singers, ca. 1970-1978 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    Includes some photos of Mavis Staples as a solo artist
  - Tavares (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous T, ca. 1975-1995 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Two Tons O' Fun, ca. 1980 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    See also Sylvester, box 71, folder 18
  - Willie Tyler and Lester (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Jr. Walker and the All-Stars, ca. 1968-1979 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Tammi Terrell, ca. 1966-1970 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Carla Thomas (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Flip Wilson (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Dee Dee Warwick, undated (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Narada Michael Walden, ca. 1979 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - J.J. Walker (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Adam Wade (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Ray Vitte, ca. 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Ben Vereen, ca. 1976-1978 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Vanity (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Tata Vega, ca. 1976-1979 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Sarah Vaughan, ca. 1969-1978 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous U (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Undisputed Truth, ca. 1972-1979 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Leslie Uggams, ca. 1972-1978 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Deniece Williams (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Dionne Warwick (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Spinners, ca. 1973-1980 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    See also Philippe Wynne, box 73, folder 20
  - Kim Weston, ca. 1968-1974 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Billy Dee Williams (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Luther Vandross, ca. 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous V, ca. 1968-1978 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Mary Wells (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Whispers (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Jackie Wilson, ca. 1966-1970 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Norman Whitfield, undated (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous W-Z (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Philippe Wynne (Box 73, Folder 20)
    See also Spinners, box 73, folder 10
  - Temptations -- miscellaneous prints, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    See also Temptations -- proof sheets and negatives, box 76, folder 8; Temptations -- Dennis Edwards, box 76, folder 6; Temptations -- Melvin Franklin, box 76, folder 7
  - Temptations -- David Ruffin, ca. 1969-1979 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Temptations -- Eddie Kendricks (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Barry White -- miscellaneous prints, ca. 1974-1979 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Barry White -- Bruce Talamon, ca. 1974-1976 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Includes photographs of Barry White taken by photographer Bruce Talamon
  - Barry White -- Howard Bingham (Box 74, Folder 5)
    Includes photographs of Barry White taken by photographer Howard Bingham
  - Barry White -- Bobby Holland, ca. 1978 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    Includes photographs of Barry White taken by photographer Bobby Holland
  - Sylvers, ca. 1973-1980 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Stevie Wonder -- miscellaneous prints (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Stevie Wonder -- proof sheets, ca. 1969-1980 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Tina Turner, ca. 1970-1977 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    Includes photographs from the Ike and Tina Turner era
  - Donna Summer (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Diana Ross -- miscellaneous prints, ca. 1969-1983 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Diana Ross -- proof sheets and negatives, ca. 1973-1979 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Diana and Supremes (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Supremes (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Includes photographs and proofs of the group after Diana Ross's departure
  - Marvin Gaye -- miscellaneous prints, ca. 1969-1978 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Marvin Gaye -- movie, ca. 1971 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    Includes publicity photographs from Chrome and Hot Leather, a movie which starred Marvin Gaye
  - Marvin Gaye -- proof sheets and negatives (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Brothers Johnson, undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Originals, ca. 1970-1978 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Jayne Kennedy (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Jones Girls (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Millie Jackson, ca. 1978-1982 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Blinky, ca. 1968-1970 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Lionel Ritchie (Box 76, Folder 3)
    See also Commodores, box 65, folders 1-2
  - Shirley Bassey, ca. 1975-1978 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Pearl Bailey, ca. 1979 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Temptations -- Dennis Edwards (Box 76, Folder 6)
    See also Temptations -- miscellaneous prints, box 73, folder 21
  - Temptations -- Melvin Franklin, ca. 1973-1980 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Temptations -- proof sheets and negatives, ca. 1973-1979 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Ray Charles (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Smokey Robinson -- proof sheets and negatives, ca. 1968-1977 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    See also Smokey Robinson, box 71, folder 8; Miracles box 69, folder 10
  - Patti Austin, ca. 1980-1990 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Drifters (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Gary Coleman, ca. 1979-1981 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Ja'net Dubois, ca. 1975-1980 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Erma Franklin (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Patti LaBelle (Box 76, Folder 16)
    Also see Labelle, box 69, folder 1
  - Jackson Five, ca. 1972-1975 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 76, Folder 18)
    A loose photograph of an unidentified individual
- 5. Administrative Files, 1973-1980
  Stock certificates, meeting minutes, by-laws, articles of incorporation, honorary citizen award, and issues of other newspapers affiliated with SOUL's publishers.
  - Bound booklet of SOUL Publications, Inc. stock certificates, ca. 1973 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - SOUL Publications, Inc. minutes binder (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Includes articles of incorporation, by-laws, board of directors' meeting minutes, and other official documentation
  - Honorary Citizen of New Orleans award (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Certificate presented to SOUL Publisher Regina Jones by New Orleans Mayor Moon Landrieu and councilmen
  - Los Angeles Post, Volume 1, Number 1, 1978 December 21 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles Post, Volume 1, Number 3, 1979 January 4 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Post, Volume 1, Number 9 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles Spirit, Volume 1, Number 11, 1979 May 3 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles Spirit, Volume 1, Number 12, 1979 May 10 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Spirit, Volume 1, Number 13 (Box 77, Folder 9)